Damn you!
I'm really sorry.
How many times do you have to do this
before you're satisfied?
We're always telling you
to wash your hands with hot water.
Don't be so hard on him.
Jiji is doing his best, too.
Okarun, are you okay?
Yes, somehow.
Okarun, I'm so sorry!
Please, don't worry about it at all.
Evil Eye has gotten
a lot stronger than before.
Hey, Grandma,
isn't this getting a bit out of hand?
Jiji can't be careful
about everything, either!
Yeah. We might not have
a house anymore by tomorrow.
Don't wanna hear that "might"!
Pardon the intrusion!
If you're gonna intrude, go home.
Okey-dokey.
When are the hayashi folks coming?
Who knows?
Why don't we at least
settle on a formation?
We're all over the place, especially Aira.
Huh? I'm the leader!
You need to follow me!
If we followed a dumbass,
we'd all go down!
What was that? You pig head!
- Ugly, ugly, ugly!
- Pig, pig, pig!
Um, excuse me.
Would this happen to be
Ms. Seiko Ayase's residence?
So what if it is?
Oh, so it is.
Um, we are...
...the ones who received your request.
PATARSON
YOSHIKICHI
HIDEJI
TOSHIRO
We are HAYASii.
We are HAYASii!
EPISODE 18
WE BECAME A FAMILY
If that's the case, then just say so.
We do have an image to maintain,
so we're sorry.
Wicked.
This is different from what I thought,
and it's getting me hyped up!
So awesome!
You're kidding me.
Are they spirit mediums?
Nope. They can't even sense spirits.
- But their performance is the real deal.
- Test, test. Mic check.
They have the power to echo their sounds
into the spiritual world.
Besides, if they can't sense spirits...
they won't get dragged along
by evil spirits during an exorcism.
Whoa, oh no!
All right, you bastards!
Let's put some spirit into this!
Yeah!
I said, let's put some spirit into this!
Come on!
Yeah!
All right, bring it on! Let's go!
Are you all ready?!
Yeah!
Time for an exorcism!
Dark and corroded world in despair
Ravenous beasts are wandering
Lying in wait for me like a hex
Blackest of destinations
Echoing through the frostbitten sky
Song of the grimmest lullaby
Pain that you suffered, plain from your scars
Hark, I can hear your requiem
Starting to crumble down
In a cacophony of screams
Spirit in lunacy
Coming apart at the seams
HUNTING SOUL, Insatiate and wild
Roaming the land for a blood sacrifice
HUNTING SOUL, Night after night
So go to sleep if you dare
In the back! Are you watching?
I won't leave anyone behind!
Let's go!
Bring it on!
Stop it!
Pallid the wasteland, Filling the air
Howls of a fallen angel
Momo! Hold Jiji down!
Wings that are twisted, Ready to break
Yearning for something true to love
Use your psychic powers.
Don't get near him!
I know!
Into oblivion
Feeling it call unto thee
Don't erase him!
Now uncontrollable
Feral is your JEALOUSY
This is...
Don't kill Evil Eye!
No more pain
Hey! Put some spirit into it!
I promised I would play with him!
He just wanted to play with someone!
He was trapped all that time,
but he kept dreaming of the day
that he'd get to play with someone.
He even practiced dancing, but now
that he's out, he's just going to die again?
That's way too sad!
I'll try really hard
and not use cold water anymore!
So please! Please don't kill Evil Eye!
HUNTING SOUL, Fire aglow
Scorching the earth as it crosses the skies
Please!
HUNTING SOUL, LOSING CONTROL
CHASIN' YOU DOWN TO THE END
I'm begging you!
HUNTING SOUL!
Um...
Call it off.
No exorcism.
I'll have Evil Eye join my family.
Huh? What? What did you just say?
Sorry to do this after coming
all the way here, but you can go home now.
Oh, I see. I understand.
You sure, Grandma?
You heard Jiji.
Can't do anything about it.
I personally like that kind of spirit in Jiji.
Then, what? We have to keep
taking care of this guy forever?
I totally don't want to!
I don't want my precious time
to be wasted because of his selfishness!
Then, I'll learn how to hold Evil Eye back.
If I can become stronger
and easily hold Evil Eye back,
there wouldn't be any problems
even if he were to transform, right?
But is that something you need to go
out of your way to do, Takakura?
You won't be able to sleep
peacefully anymore!
Your life will be in danger.
He's my friend.
Then I'll become stronger, too.
It's easier if there's two of us, right?
Hold on!
I'll become stronger as well!
So that I can send you flying!
I'd like to see you try, you ugly hag!
Okarun, let me hug you.
Okarun!
You guys!
- Okarun!
- Hot water!
Sorry to have bothered you!
If you need anything again,
please contact us!
TOSHIRO
Yeah. Great work.
We might call you again real soon.
Grandma, it's cold in the house now.
For now, grab some cardboard boxes
from the supermarket.
Sit on your legs, back straight.
Clench up your lower abs.
Imagine a laser beam coming out of the top
of your head and your fingertips.
Don't fall over even when you get pushed.
Sit like you're rooted to the ground.
Sure.
Jiji, like this.
Back straight. Try pushing me.
Try pushing really hard.
Huh? Really?
Whoa, you won't fall over!
Seriously? This is amazing!
You were so reluctant to do this,
but you learned it after all.
I didn't think it would actually be useful.
Back in grade school, you made
some weird poses. Was it this?
I can use psychic powers
when I'm in this condition.
This is the state where chi is flowing out.
When you enter this state,
you'll be able to use spiritual energy.
Your spiritual energy is off the charts.
With all that energy, maybe you'll
be able to hold Evil Eye back by yourself.
Hup.
Whoa, you scared me.
Mr. Jiji, please wash your hands
with hot water.
Okay.
It's getting warm now.
Thanks.
Thanks, Okarun.
It's nothing.
Oof.
Oh my. The cardboard
is coming apart over there.
Mr. Jiji, don't get close to it.
There's dew on it and stuff.
I'm sorry all this happened because of me.
Please don't apologize.
We're looking out for each other.
When I was cursed by Turbo Granny,
I troubled the Ayase family as well.
But they really devoted themselves
to taking care of me.
I wanted to properly repay them
for living expenses and clothing costs,
so I delivered newspapers and
took some money to them. But then...
What good would it do to repay me?
If you feel gratitude
for us taking care of you,
you should pay it forward
to someone else who's in trouble.
That's what it means
to look out for each other.
Auntie is so awesome!
I thought I wanted
to say things like that, too.
In my case, I'm just acting tough.
But I want to look cool, even if
it's just a little bit, so I'm mimicking her.
There is absolutely no crisis management.
Time to eat.
Takakura, what about seconds?
There's more miso soup, too!
Make sure to eat lots.
Oh, sure.
Jiji, gotta clench your lower abs
and straighten your back.
Emit chi at all times.
Yes'm.
More, please.
Go get some yourself.
Damn you, you did it for Okarun.
Of course I did.
What was that, ugly girl?
You wanna go?
- Pig, pig, pig, pig!
- Ugly, ugly, ugly, ugly!
Take care!
- Takakura, did you forget anything?
- Hey! Take care!
- Did you prepare for your classes today?
- Yes.
- Huh? Take care.
- Man, my stomach hurts.
I think I got too chilly
because the house was too cold.
Do your best, everyone!
You were sleeping
with your stomach out.
Motivation! Courage! Spirit!
Tenacity! Sincerity!
Then put the comforter on me!
Takakura, let me tell you. Momo Ayase
thrashes around in her sleep!
Motivation! Courage! Spirit! Sincerity!
Huh? What was it? Sincerity! Tenacity!
Hey, stop that!
And she uses other people's toner
without asking.
You said it was okay!
- Aira grinds her teeth really loud!
- Hey, damn it! Don't be lying here!
Everyone take care on your way!
That's it! I'm gonna get a part-time job!
What's gotten into you?
I'm going to rebuild the house!
Wicked!
- What about your smartphone?
- Like I need something like that.
Right now, we're seeking warmth.
Was your house that cold?
I mean, it's frigid, of course!
Wasn't Ririna saying that she was looking
for some part-time help?
Oh, she was. Was it for a restaurant?
Seriously? Tell her I'll totally do it!
But Momo, you never last long
in a part-time job.
You always argue with the boss and stuff.
I just hate the unreasonable.
So cool.
It's hard for a gal to recommend
someone who quits so quickly, though.
It's fine! I have grown up!
I won't give up oh so easily!
Did you hear that, Ms. Muko?
I did hear it, Ms. Mi.
Okarun!
Momo said she got a part-time job today,
so you can go home without her.
All right. I understand.
- And...
- ...so!
You should go on a date with us!
What? I decline!
Come with us, you punk!
Don't resist!
Hold on, wait!
I'm not gonna go on a date!
We're just gonna have some tea!
Don't you call that a date?
Then if Momo and Jiji were having tea,
would that be a date?
Of course not.
Then tell us what's so different
when it's us, damn it!
No way!
KAMIGOE SHOPPING STREET
I really don't want to!
Okarun, this way! Over here!
I'm not going to drink one drop of tea!
You'll get thirsty.
No, I won't!
Absolutely sure?
You better not drink anything, then!
I won't drink!
Welcome home, master!
How many in your party?
Three!
Hey, you maid over there!
Make sure to serve us well.
Wait, Okarun?
M-Miss Ayase!
Come on now.
Welcome home, master!
There's not enough food!
Bring me some more!
Everything's expensive, you idiot!
A house with no food? I'll just run away!
Fine, then, leave!
Yeah? I'm never coming back
to this damn house, then!
Next episode,
"Feeling Kinda Gloomy."
EPISODE 19
FEELING KINDA GLOOMY